macitbetter.com 2019-06-11

# Imprint and Privacy Policy - MacItBetter

## Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy is simple: We do not collect any personally identifiable information when you visit our website or use our apps. The website macitbetter.com does not have any visitor tracking and does not include external resources (Javascripts, images, etc.) hosted on third-party web servers. 

When purchasing a license we have to store the billing contact information that was provided during the payment process (name, address, e-mail address, IP address) for taxation purposes. However, your data will not be shared with third parties. 

Payment processing is handled by our partner BMT Micro, Inc. whose privacy policy you can find [here](https://www.bmtmicro.com/support/misc_forms/PrivacyStatement.html). They do not share your credit card information or other sensitive payment data with us. 

## Data Transmission

All data transmissions to our servers, website, and shop are secured using strong, state-of-the-art encryption. 

## Data Security

Our web server is managed and secured by pair Networks, Inc. 

## Logging

When you connect to our web server, either by visiting our website or through our applications' built-in update checker, you generate requests to our server. Our web server maintains logs of these requests containing your IP address, browser and OS kinds and versions. We may look at that data in aggregate to gather statistical information such as market share of macOS versions or similar. The server log files are deleted on a regular basis. 

## Customer Support

When you contact us for a support request, we keep a record of your communication, including your e-mail address and all information that you’ve provided to us with your request. We do not use this information for any other purpose than answering your support request. 

## Crash Reports

If one of our apps crashes while you are using it, data about the crash can, with your consent, be transmitted to us to help identify the cause of the crash so that we can try to fix it in a future update. These crash reports contain information about the state of the app, operating system, and device at the time of the crash. You can either transmit the crash report anonymously or add your e-mail address to give us a chance to get in touch with you. Similar to other support requests, any transmitted information will only be used to solve the problem and will not be shared with third parties. 

## E-Mail List

If you sign up for our e-mail newsletter, your e-mail address will be added to our e-mail list. The newsletter is low volume (no more than two messages a year), and is generally limited to announcements of important new versions of our apps, or significant new product releases. Again, your e-mail address will not be shared with third parties, with the exception of the company that provides the mailing list services, [The Rocket Science Group LLC (MailChimp)](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/). 

## Personal Information from Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 14. If we come to know that we have collected personal information from a child under 14, this information will be promptly deleted. 

## Changes to This Policy

We may add new services and features to our website or products. If these additions affect our privacy policy, it will be updated accordingly. 

MacItBetter is  
Robert Rezabek  
Redlschlag 67  
A-7434 Bernstein, Austria
